Now that we know the basic phrases for talking about the future let's just explore a little bit some
现在我们知道了谈论未来的基本短语，让我们稍微探索一下
phrases that we can use to talk about the relationship between cause and result and also our actions
我们可以用来谈论原因和结果之间的关系以及我们的行为的短语
and our intentions.
和我们的意图。
The cause of our actions is often our intentions our intentions is what we really want to do.
我们行动的原因往往是我们的意图，我们的意图是我们真正想做的事情。
What comes up in our mind that makes us act right.
我们脑海中浮现的让我们采取正确行动的事情。
So let's look at some ways that we can do that.
因此，让我们看看我们可以做到这一点的一些方法。
If you want to be successful you need to work hard so we can use if to express intentions or express
如果你想成功，你需要努力，所以我们可以用if来表达意图或表达
desire and then an action related to that desire.
欲望，然后是与该欲望相关的动作。
If you want this do this or you need to do this.
如果你想这样做，或者你需要这样做。
If you want to quit smoking you need to have a lot of willpower willpower.
如果你想戒烟，你需要有很大的意志力意志力。
If you want to be successful you need to work hard.
如果你想成功，你需要努力工作。
You can switch this around you could say you need to work hard if you want to be successful.
你可以改变这个，你可以说如果你想成功就需要努力工作。
If you do it that way you need to work hard.
如果你这样做，你需要努力工作。
If you want to be successful cancel this comma don't use that.
如果您想成功取消此逗号，请不要使用该逗号。
So if you switch it around and it starts with you don't use the comma if it starts with.
因此，如果您切换它并且它以开头，则不要使用逗号。
If use the comma.
如果使用逗号。
OK so that why do we do things.
好的，那我们为什么要这样做。
Why do you do what you do.
你为什么要做你所做的。
You have a reason an intention.
你有理由有意图。
There is a cause for your actions.
你的行为是有原因的。
I workout workout means exercise I workout so that this is our intention.
我锻炼锻炼意味着锻炼我锻炼，所以这是我们的意图。
I workout so that I can stay in shape.
我锻炼是为了保持身材。
Remember we learn to stay in shape or get in shape to when we want to state why we say this.
请记住，当我们想说明为什么要这样说时，我们会学会保持体型或保持体型。
Save the same thing here.
在此处保存相同的内容。
I work hard so that someday I can be successful.
我努力工作，以便有一天我能成功。
Same basic idea I read to broaden my horizons.
我阅读了相同的基本想法以拓宽视野。
I read to broaden my horizons.
我读书是为了开阔我的视野。
Now this too is not used in the same way as to connected to a verb like go.
现在，这也与连接到像 go 这样的动词不同。
I'm going to the supermarket.
我要去超市。
It's not that too.
也不是这样。
This too is about our intentions are reasons for doing things I read.
这也是关于我们的意图是做我读到的事情的原因。
Why do you read to broaden my horizons.
为什么你读书是为了开阔我的视野。
That means to expand what I can think about to expand what I know to expand what I'm aware of.
这意味着扩大我能想到的东西，扩大我所知道的东西，扩大我所知道的东西。
To broaden my horizons by the way a very useful phrase.
顺便说一句非常有用的话来拓宽我的视野。
We could say the same thing here.
我们可以在这里说同样的话。
I work out to stay in shape if we use so that I can stay in shape to stay in shape or get in shape.
如果我们使用，我会努力保持体形，这样我就可以保持体形以保持体形或保持体形。